http://dryicons.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
We know how much you value and care about your personal information and how it is used. Within this Privacy statement you can find details on how we collect and use, and under which circumstances may share your information.
General Information
We collect the e-mail addresses of people who communicate with us by e-mail, and name when obtaining our products and services. We collect information only for the purposes of improving the content and the quality of our website pages and our services, and to provide you the products and services acquired at our website. Information are not shared with or sold to any other party, except that we may release information in the following cases:
When we tell you we will and we have your permission.
It is required to share information under the law in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
If DryIcons.com is acquired by or merged with another company, and in such event, we will notify you by email or by putting a notice on our web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Cookies
A cookie is a small portion of data, often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site's servers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Every computer that accesses our website is assigned a different cookie by us. We use cookies for analytics, to improve your experience, track your session and store the contents of your shopping cart.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make significant changes to our Privacy Policy which would affect the way we collect and use any of your personal information, and under which circumstances share any information, we will notify you by a notice on our website pages.
Questions
Any questions you may have about our Privacy Policy should be addressed to [email protected]
